ddpyoga.com 2019-05-15

# Privacy Policy | DDP Yoga

DDP YOGA Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from ddpyoga.com or ddpyoganow.com (the “Site”).

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”.

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

  * “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
  * “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
  * “Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers) email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information”.

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To process transactions:  
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

  * Communicate with you;
  * Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
  * When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

To personalize your experience:  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

To improve our website:  
We continually strive to improve and optimize our Site offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

To improve customer service:  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails:  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company newsletters, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email.

**SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site -- you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

**BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING**

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. DDP YOGA uses a remarketing advertising service. When visitors come to our site, third parties (such as AdRoll) may place cookies on your browsers for targeted advertising purposes.  Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website, to help us remember and process the items in your cart, and to understand and save your preferences for future visits. Also, cookies may be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites. In effect, that may cause you to see our ads on other sites you visit.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by using the links below:

  * Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
  * Google: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
  * Bing: https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
  * Adroll: https://www.adrollgroup.com/privacy (visit your choices and opting-out section)

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.

**INFORMATION PROTECTION**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

**DO NOT TRACK**

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

**YOUR RIGHTS**

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

**DATA RETENTION**

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

**YOUR CONSENT**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**CHANGES**

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

**CONTACT US**

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e‑mail at orders@ddpyoga.com or by mail using the details provided below:

DDP YOGA  
Attn: Privacy Compliance Officer  
1239 Concord Road SE  
Smyrna, GA. 30080

This policy was last modified on 05.04.2018
